<rooms>
    <room keyword="Space" name="Space">
        <description>There is no atmosphere or light. The eerie silence is unearthly. Up a ladder the airlock lies in wait.</description>
        <exits>-1,-1,-1,-1,Airlock,-1</exits>
    </room>
    <room keyword="Airlock" name="Airlock">
        <description>A massive round door leading out of the station is below your feet. The abyss of space visible through the tiny window calls your name. To the north is the entrance to the dining hall.</description>
        <exits>DHall,-1,-1,-1,-1,Space</exits>
        <item name="Screwdriver">A tool to fix broken things.</item>
        <item name="Radio">A communication device to transmit information to your crewmate.</item>
    </room>
    <room keyword="DHall" name="Dining Hall">
    <description>A massive dining room, like a cafeteria but far larger. Some of your crewmates are sitting around the dining tables eating. To the south, the airlock beckons you to return to the cold void of space. To the east, the main hallway of the station, with secrets lying in wait.</description>
        <exits>-1,Airlock,MHall,-1,-1,-1</exits>
        <item name="Astronaut Ice Cream">A delicious, albeit dry, snack that is functional and tasty!</item>
    </room>
    <room keyword="MHall" name="Main Hallway">
        <description>A long hall connecting to the command room and living quarters at the east end and the dining hall on the west.</description>
        <exits>-1,-1,SPath,DHall,-1,-1</exits>
        <item name="Hidden Knife">A counterfeit knife tucked away behind a pipe. Who could have brought this?</item>
    </room>
    <room keyword="SPath" name="Split Path">
        <description>A room with three doors, the west leading to the main hallway, the north leading to the living quarters, and the south leading to the command center.</description>
        <exits>LQuart,CCenter,-1,MHall,-1,-1</exits>
    </room>
    <room keyword="LQuart" name="Living Quarters">
        <description>A long room with sleeping pods in an array across the walls. The smell of aftershave fills the artificial air, and the sound of music can be faintly heard coming from one of your crewmate's headphones. The secret ladder peers out from beneath your bed, only visible to the observant eye.</description>
        <exits>-1,SPath,-1,-1,-1,SBunker</exits>
        <item name="Deodorant">Wouldn't want to smell bad in space!</item>
        <item name="Toothbrush">Corporation provided toothbrush. The bristles are thin and the handle is flimsy.</item>
        <item name="Family Portrait">A picture of your family, the reason you're on this mission. Don't forget.</item>
    </room>
    <room keyword="CCenter" name="Command Center">
        <description>A room with beeping gadgets and levers lining the walls. The flashing lights gleam harmonically with one another creating a mesmerizing pattern.</description>
        <exits>SPath,-1,-1,-1,-1,-1</exits>
        <item name="ID Card">Your identification, command says there's a massive penalty for losing it. Better hold on tight!</item>
    </room>
    <room keyword="SBunker" name="Secret Bunker">
        <description>The concealed room that you have been maintaining since you began your mission. On the walls are pictures from your past, flashing memories in your eyes. The ladder back to the living quarters is shaky and wobbles under your feet.</description>
        <exits>-1,-1,-1,-1,LQuart,-1</exits>
        <item name="Computer">The computer you stole from command. Their daily reminders that theft is punishable by expulsion bring you fear, but you hold onto your prized possession.</item>
    </room>
</rooms>